#### KYRYLO RYBALKO

#### E-MAIL: RYBALKOKYRYLO@GMAIL.COM

As a multilingual professional, I have gained diverse experience in customer service, logistics, and management. Passionate about technology, I transitioned to a tech career by completing an intensive programming bootcamp, which equipped me with the necessary skills to excel in the industry. Additionally, with a degree in International Relations, I possess a unique combination of skills that allows me to make valuable contributions and create a meaningful impact in the fast-paced world of technology.

# **Professional Experience**

#### Tech Trainee, La Fosse - 01/2020 - Present

Engaged in various activities using AGILE methodology in full-time intensive programming bootcamp.

Technologies used: JavaScript(Node.js, Express, React), Python(Flask), HTML&CSS, TailwindCSS, Git, Github, Docker, MongoDB and PostgreSQL.

# Operations Performance Specialist - South, Whistl 01/2022 - 07/2022

Successfully onboarded and provided best experience to multiple customers within the network.

Prevented customers from leaving business with measures and improvements designed which improved our revenue - around 40 accounts saved.

## Transport Clerk, Whistl 09/2020 - 12/2021

Created and implemented new report which drastically increased transparency and permitted managing high-valued goods/loads more effectively.

Created a system which assured all the resources in use are accountable.

#### Team Leader, Whistl 09/2019 - 09/2020

Leaded a team of 15 to 25 operatives to achieve daily objectives/targets in order to meet customer expectations.

Promoted professional growth by delegated duties to the team members. Successfully trained my colleagues.

#### Education

## Harvard University, Cambridge, USA(Online Program) 2022

### **CS50P - Introduction to Programming with Python**

# University of Evora, Portugal 2015 - 2018 Bachelor's Degree in International Relations

Economics • History
 Political Science
 Law

Certificate of participation in DiploEx - simulation of NATO Crisis Management Process by EADA Portugal - 04/2017 and 04/2016